http://www.productionadvantageonline.com/privacy-policy/

Customer Login
If you are already registered, please log in.
Email Address:
Password:
Forgot your password?
Create your account and enjoy a new shopping experience.
Create A New Account
×
We are open for business.
We have limited shipping capability, call us for up to date availability on products.
My Account
Hello.
Sign in
Customer Login
×
If you are already registered, please log in.
Email Address:
Password:
Forgot your password?
Create your account and enjoy a new shopping experience.For those who had an account on our old site, the accounts were not migrated for security reasons.
Please create a new account.
Create A New Account
My Account
Wish Lists
0
My Cart
Equipment
Lighting
Moving Lights
Overview
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Production Advantage, Inc. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the proadv.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Production Advantage, Inc..
Personal Identification Information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, fill out a form, respond to a survey, subscribe to the newsletter and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information,
Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.
We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We provide limited analytics information to our website and marketing development partner, Brandthropology, Inc., with whom we have signed an agreement preventing them from selling or renting this data.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web Browser Cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
As part of this activity, proadv.com participates in the Google Analytics program. Click here to learn more. We also participate in the Facebook Analytics programs. Click here to learn more.
How we use collected information
Production Advantage, Inc. collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:
To improve customer serviceYour information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
To personalize user experienceWe may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our SiteWe continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
To process transactionsWe may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other Site featureTo send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
To send periodic emailsThe email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also utilizes PCI-compliant payment processors that adhere to PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
We do not sell or rent this information to anyone. We provide limited analytics information to our website and marketing development partner, Brandthropology, Inc., with whom we have signed an agreement preventing them from selling or renting this data.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website\'s own terms and policies.
BigCommerce Specific PCI
ProAdv is built on the Enterprise-Grade ecommerce platform, BigCommerce.
The following is BigCommerce's PCI Compliance statement.
BigCommerce is a PCI-DSS Level 1 Service Provider, as such our storage of Account Data is audited annually by a Qualified Security Assessor (QSA).
The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard defines Account Data in the following way;
Cardholder Data
Primary Account Number
Cardholder Name
Expiration Date
Sensitive Authentication Data
Security Code (CVV)
While the standard does have a provision for the storage of Cardholder Data prior to the completion of the credit transaction, it does not make allowance for the storage of Sensitive Authentication Data.
However, to reduce exposure of Cardholder Data, it is BigCommerce policy to not store any Account Data.
BigCommerce performs ongoing security scans to ensure compliance with the data security across our platform. If a merchant is storing data that violates any of the policy mentioned above, the data will be expunged and the merchant will be alerted of the violation.
Stored Credit Card Feature
In BigCommerce the Stored Credit Cards does NOT store credit card information in the store. The payment gateway stores this information which is in keeping with PCI compliance.
Changes to this privacy policy
Production Advantage, Inc. has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page,. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
Production Advantage, Inc.PO Box 1700Williston, VT 054951-800-424-9991
customerservice@proadv.com
Last Updated 9 July 2019 12:35 EST
×
Need help? We're available at1-800-424-9991
-
Email us atcustomerservice@proadv.com
On Time Delivery
When the show must go on...on time...trust our cutting edge logistics to deliver, whether shipping from our fully stocked warehouse or direct from our manufacturer partners.
Secure Shopping
Industry-leading security for your transactions ensures that your information is safe.
Shop with Confidence
With hassle-free returns and real service after the sale, you can shop our site with confidence. Not sure which solution is right for you? Our expert sales staff is here to help every step of the way.
Experienced Support Staff
Remember real customer service?
We sure do!
We’re more than just another pretty website, we handle every order with a human touch.
Further Info.
Receive our latest updates about our products and promotions.
Join our mailing list
© 2020 Production Advantage
